<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CST</string>

    <string name="why">CST is a place where brilliant minds assemble and collaborate,where they
        pool together their individual talents across departments in service of big ideas and
        creative solutions. It is a vibrant community teeming with students collaborating with
        experts and specialists: a hub of innovation and creativity. It is an intersection of
        diversity, a launching pad for a brilliant career, and a highly unique state of mind. It
        is a perfect environment in which to pursue your passion. Here, the future is envisioned
        each day. And remade each day after.</string>

    <string name="Fashion">Apart from studies, our keen enthusiasm to engross in non academic remains highly
        motivated and hugely inspired. It showcase and testimony that young one needs to
        groom with exceptional perspicacity in later career. Pursuing this objective, NDLD
        club organize fashion show to inculcate the senses of enthrallment and engagement
        to all our students. The club ensures to participate every individual from each
        department. This harbingers to manifest the dimensional talents of our students.
        Most importantly it gets most of our students involved which is fundamental of
        participation is better than winning. The themes distributed based on their individual
        selections. The vastness of theme includes: weather, session, education, water,
        happiness etc .It is not compulsory for every students to be the audience and witness
        the show. The fact is everyone make their way to this very show and hall would fraught
        with laugh and immense discourse.  The participants are made to walk among the audience
        wearing jazzy dress keeping their theme in the mind. Most interestingly refreshments are
        also served to all the audience .The varieties of the cultural show are also performed
        so that every parts of the activities become more meaningful.  The attractive and
        stunning prizes are also awarded to all the participants and remarking prizes are
        arranged for winner and runner up.
        </string>

    <string name="Tag">Tag night is a moment where student especially first year girls get an opportunity to
        showcase their talent. Tag night is organized by final year students where our mess is
        decorated and they also prepare a stage where people can ramp walk on it. All the
        students make their presence in the mess in the given time and the program starts by
        the welcoming the first-year students. Firstly, our college Chief Councilor have to
        share few words then do ramp walk which is then followed by our Girl VC then comes our
        formal Miss CST, Miss Tag and Miss Ever Green. Above mentioned are the judges for
        the night. They judge the first-year girls based on their confidence at first round.
        For the second round 15 girls are being selected from the first round then they have
        to show their talent and answer some questions that is asked by the judges. Girl with
        the highest points from all judges is being selected as a Miss CST. Not only that
        during the tag night girl with the highest tag gets the title as Miss Tag then the
        boy who has purchased more tag is given a title as Mr. Expensive. As Miss CST and Miss
        Tag is selected from first year and Mr. Expensive can be anyone that buys more tag.
        Mr. Gentle man is being judged by the judges and only final year boys can compete for
        the Mr. Gentleman title. Finally comes our Miss Evergreen. This title is being awarded
        to someone from the third-year female with a feature of remaining same, young and
        beautiful from first-year till the third-year. At last Tag night winds up by awarding
        all the titles to the deserving souls.

    </string>

    <string name="Intro">Introduction night which is also commonly called as Intro night is
        being held every odd semester to welcome the fresher\’s. It is organized by students
        of Third year. During the event fresher\’s are firstly given small and beautifully
        handmade badges. Then after the arrival of all the students in the hall, first years
        are asked to go up on the well decorated stage and introduce themselves. In the
        introduction it includes their name, name of their previous school and their relationship
        status. Fresher\’s can also show their talents if they have any. Their talents will be
        judged by the Chief Councilor and other councilors and those fresher with best
        introduction will be awarded with gifts. The event is ended by the jam session where
        everyone dance to their fullest.
    </string>

    <string name="Prayer">Whether we pray aloud or pray silently in our hearts in fleeting
        moments of need, prayer is a personal form of communication where we can speak
        directly with our Father in Heaven. Prayers are conducted on Thursday especially
        after classes are over. For hall arrangement first or second year-students have to be
        to be present alternatively. All the students are compulsory except final year as they
        can join if they are interested. Students pray for almost one and half hours but during
        auspious day, student pray for  almost 2 and half hours.
    </string>

    <string name="Diwali">The festival gets its name from the row (avali) of clay lamps (deepa) that
        southern bhutanses light outside their homes to symbolize the inner light that protects from
        spiritual darkness.  The festival usually falls between the middle of October and the middle
        of November, although this is decided upon by the Hindu lunar calendar. While each faith has
        its own reason to celebrate the festival, one of the most popular stories told is the legend
        of Lord Rama and his wife Sita returning to their kingdom in northern India from exile after
        defeating the demon king Ravanna in the 15th century BC. Diwali in our college is organized
        by the Third year students. They prepare a prayer followed by fun activities for the students.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_nav">Nav</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="course">Courses</string>
    <string name="Civil">

        Bachelor of Engineering in Civil Engineering takes minimum of four years full time. The programme would provide
        access to larger numbers of suitably qualified nationals to be trained as engineers to meet the needs of Bhutan.
        The increased supply of engineers would also support private sector growth thereby creating additional jobs and
        strengthening the economy. The courses have been designed to meet the requirements of Bhutan’s unique engineering
        demand. The graduates will find employment in Civil Service, Corporations and Private sector.\n\n

    The programme aims to be innovative in course and curriculum development in order\n\n

    i. To attract and recruit students of good academic ability and potential from all social groups.\n\n
    ii. To develop the potential of each student to meet new challenges and to lay the foundation of versatility of
        thinking they will need in careers as professional engineers.\n\n
    iii. To provide students with an engineering education with breadth across the engineering disciplines, combined
        with some specialist learning, delivered with design as an integrating feature.\n\n
    iv. To understand the importance of professionalism, management, and problem solving techniques for works.\n\n
    v. To allow career progression and educational development to study for a Masters degree
    Civil engineering students learn how to analyze and solve problems related to construction and maintenance of bridges,
        buildings, airports, waterways, and water and waste-water treatment facilities, hydraulic structures.\n\n
      vi.  they also learn how to communicate their solutions of these problems (their designs) to others and how to transform their
        designs into reality. Civil engineering is a challenging, creative and satisfying career.\n\n

    Students also have a unique opportunity to experience aspects of the civil engineering profession by making visits to sites.\n

        Civil Engineering graduates are expected to be able to:\n\n

    1. formulate and prepare project proposals and plans.\n\n
    2. design, analyse, prepare working drawings and estimates of various civil engineering structures
    execute/supervise the construction of various civil engineering structures.\n\n
    3. carry out survey for civil engineering works.\n\n
    4. carry out feasibility studies for civil engineering projects.\n\n
    5. prepare bid documents, specifications of works and evaluate tenders\n\n
    6. adapt to new technologies/developments.\n\n
    7. manage projects and other civil engineering related tasks.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="electrical">

        The Bachelor of Engineering in Electrical Engineering takes minimum of four years full time.

        The programme provides access to larger numbers of suitably qualified nationals to be trained as engineers
        to meet the needs of Bhutan. The increased supply of engineers would also support private sector growth thereby
        creating additional jobs and strengthening the economy. The courses have been designed to meet the requirements
        of Bhutan’s unique engineering demand. The graduates will find employment in Civil Service, Corporations and
        Private sector.\n\n

        The Institute aims to be innovative in course and curriculum development in order\n\n

        i. To attract and recruit students of good academic ability and potential from all social groups.\n\n
        ii. To develop the potential of each student to meet new challenges and to lay the foundation of versatility
        of thinking they will need in careers as professional engineers.\n\n
        iii. To provide students with an engineering education with breadth across the engineering disciplines,
        combined with some specialised learning, delivered with design and problem solving as an integral feature.\n\n
        iv. To understand the importance of professionalism, management, and problem solving techniques for works.\n\n
        v. To allow career progression and educational development to study for a Masters degree
        Electrical engineering is a challenging but exciting and rewarding area of study. It is a rapidly advancing
        field that is having a significant impact on shaping modern society. By studying electrical engineering students
        will be able to understand the significant developments in modern technology and be prepared to play a role
        in shaping its future.\n\n

        Students also have a unique opportunity to experience aspects of the Electrical engineering profession by
        making short visits to sites.
        The Undergraduate Degree programme in Electrical Engineering centers about analysis, design of components
        and system and transform the designs into reality.\n\n

        The electrical engineering graduate are expected to be able to:\n\n

       1. Plan and implement electrical power system, control system and communication system.\n\n
       2. formulate/prepare proposals and project plans.\n\n
        3. design and estimate electrical installation works/systems.\n\n
        4. execute/supervise the implementation of electrical works with quality control measures.\n\n
        5. use relevant software for electrical engineering works.\n\n
        6. conduct research studies to enhance professional development.\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="electronic">

    Specific Objectives of the Degree Programme in Electronics and Communication Engineering.\n\n

    The Electronics and Communication Engineering graduates are expected to be able to:\n\n

    1. plan, analyze, design and develop application of devices and systems involving electronic components.\n\n
    2. plan, analyze, design, implement and manage communication system and network infrastructure with quality
        control measures and be environmentally conscious.\n\n
   3.  identify, analyze, formulate and solve electronics and communication engineering problems.\n\n
    4. formulate/prepare proposals and project plans.\n\n
   5.  critically evaluate information, create and critique logical arguments using quantitative reasoning.\n\n
  6.  work in multi-disciplinary environment and communicate effectively.\n\n
    7. prepare for graduate works and research in at least area of ECE field of practice.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="it">

            The Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology is a new programme  scheduled to
           commence from July 2010. The curriculum was developed by the faculty of IT at CST conducting
        series of review workshop involving experts within Bhutan and professors from UNB(Canada) and IIT(Kharagpur).\n\n

            The BE(IT)  programme was approved to commence by the Programme Quality Committee of Royal University of Bhutan.\n\n

            Specific Objectives:\n
            As Information Technology graduates they are expected to be able to:\n\n

            1. Understand and demonstrate information technology applications.\n\n
            2. Plan, design, develop, test, and implement IT systems.\n\n
            3. Identify, analyse, and solve Information Technology problems.\n\n
            4. Carry out operation and maintenance of network system: Software and Hardware.\n\n
            5. Formulate/Prepare proposals for new systems and project plans.\n\n
            6. work in multi-disciplinary environment and communicate effectively.\n\n
            7. Execute/Supervise the implementation of IT system.\n\n
            8. Use relevant software and hardware for coding, code verification and testing.\n\n
            9. Take up diverse profession and lifelong learning.\n\n
            10. Conduct research studies in the field of IT.\n\n
            11. Self employment.\n\n



    </string>

    <string name="architect">

    Architecture is the physical representation of a society, this programme will is intended
        to study the soul and role of traditional Bhutanese Architecture and integrate it into the
    best present day curriculum practiced all over. This programme shall be made relevant to the
    site and scenario in Bhutanese climate, context where learners will have their study tour and
    project sites in hilly region. The learners will be encouraged solve the problem of designing
    in hilly region using the concepts of Organic Architecture and green building concepts.
    The programme is expected to incorporate the rich Bhutanese Arts, paintings and sculptures
    into the mainstream programme and is aimed to be dynamic and innovative in its course and curriculum refinement.\n\n

    Aims and objectives of the Programme.\n\n

    1. To provide excellence in Architectural Education and the design of the built environment.\n\n
    2. To preserve and promote Architecture as an important feature of Bhutanese identity.\n\
    3. To prepare the student for professional qualification of an Architect or for subsequent higher education.\n\n
    4. To develop skills in critical thinking, discussions, presentation and team work through seminar presentations,
    case studies, study tours, writings and studio activities.\n\n
    </string>


    <string name="Vision">

      \n  “A centre of excellence in science and technology enriched with GNH values. “


    </string>

    <string name="Mission">


       \n  To offer internationally recognized programs in science and technology.\n
         To generate new knowledge through research and innovation to fulfill the needs of the society.\n
         To collaborate with stakeholders and provide expert services.\n
         To provide community services to enhance GNH based society.



    </string>

    <string name="app">

    i. Merit Certificate awarded to academic Toppers.\n
    \n
    ii. Merit of Certificate awarded to students who score 80% and above.\n
    \n
    iii.Full Scholarship for finance students if they score 75% and above.\n
    \n
        iv. Students in First Semester can change their course if they score 70% and above.</string>

    <string name="responsibilities">
                Students of the university have the following responsibilities to:\n\n
                1 Apply themselves to their studies to their abilities;\n\n
                2 Become familiar with thw rules and regulations governing the degree in which thay are enrolled,and to ensure that the mdule selected meet the award requirements;\n\n
                3 Be aware of the policies practices and expectations of the university set out in the RUB Wheel of the Academy Law (RUB 2008) and of any college and department in which they are enrolled and which are contained in the module materials and information made availibale to them;\n\n
                4 Be aware of, and act according to, the rules and regulations concerning the use of the college computing , library and other facilities, and so to respect the rights of other learners;\n\n
                5 Meet the deadlines for module work to be submitted;\n\n
                6 Take the initiative and consult appropriately when problems arise in any module ;\n\n
                7 Submit original work for assessment without plagiarizing or cheating;\n\n
                8 Attend all organised teaching activities,including professional placements ,for each module in which they are enrolled and, for distance education students, to consider thoroughtly all program materials and participate in all prescribed residental schools;\n\n
                9 Accept joint responsibilty for their own learning along with the teaching staff.\n\n
                10 Provide feedback to staff about (a) teaching and learning practice and (b) the quality;\n\n
                If modules as well to contribute to the development of university programs and policies as appropriate:\n\n
                11 Abide by the university\'s policies on occupational health  and safety so that they can study in a safe and healthy environment;\n\n
                12 Be aware of the university\'s commitment to equal opportunity and to demonstratte tolerance and respect for all members of the university community including respect of the right staff members to express view;\n\n
                13 Respect the working environment of others in all areas of the university.\n\n
                NOTE: Infringement of responsibility d) and g) may lead to the disciplinary action. </string>

    <string name="title_activity_student">StudentActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="kuen">
        Kindness is doing something and not expecting anything in return. Kindness is respect and
        helping others without waiting for someone to help one back. It implies kindness no matter
        what. An act of kindness is a spontaneous gesture of goodwill towards someone or something
        –KuenphenTshokpa club performs many acts of kindness each day. They raise funds by installing
        food stall during different occasion and with the fund they have generated are used to help
        needy ones. They raised funds through the charity show and helped those poor section of the
        people. They visits the nearby places and make their path to reach in all the needy places.
    </string>

    <string name="acm">ACM local chapters engage members through talks by local practitioners, visits
        from prominent speakers from the ACM Distinguished Speakers Program, technical and career
        workshops, field trips to computing installations, and social activities.Chapters are the
        engines that drive networking and learning on a local level. It also enlists to boost the
        skills and helps to assimilate the knowledge through ACM chapter. All students from IT
        department are offered the avenue to become a member of the ACM chapter. With this, the new
        members are taught on software installation and other  necessary requirements by the seniors
        and lectures. Moreover the  day are also fixed whereby the members get together and involve
        in the meaningful discourses. So with this regard on promoting the skills , they also
        conduct the programming  contest so that the knowledge that gained from the particular
        session are awarded.



    </string>
    <string name="nature">Nature club is an autonomous organization of nature lovers from various
        departments of the college.Communing with nature is good for a student\'s psychological and
        physical well-being. It can help reduce stress, improve concentration and increase time spent
        being physically active. nature clubs are one way to encourage children to spend more time
        outside; and there are numerous opportunities to make that time spent in nature entertaining
        and educational. We believe in plantation of tress and consequence of the nature if it is
        badly depleted. We ensure that our trees are not chopped and sensitize them not to destroy.
        We celebrate the social forestry day and our nature club  organize the event.


    </string>
    <string name="bto">CST BTO members play vital roles in advocating and inculcating the sense of 
        responsibility other than just cleaning the toilets. We want to encourage the youth to engage
        in social service. If all the youth join hands to make a small contribution by every
        individual, then we would see a better tomorrow. CST\'s first action started with our own
        college to bring awareness among ourselves. Many a time toilet issue is left out, people 
        talk lot more about planting trees and managing wastes but there is a big question mark why 
        no people is concerned about the hygiene. We, CST BTO members are not going to stay idle
        watching this. The club was introduced recently on seeing the reality of the circumstances
        prevailing in our country. Besides the concerned and focal person who are obliged to do
        things, it is always   better to get together and move together. As cleanliness is next to 
        the goodness, we  will remain mindful of our duty by cleaning  the toilets in our small way.
        Not only our club work together in the college, we also volunteer ourselves and make sure to 
        visit the nearby place to render our helping hand. One  could be obvious that we monitor our
        college toilets by ensuring every students to at least clean the toilet. We sensitize and
        make awareness so that the ultimate's repercussion is always our joyous.    


    </string>
    <string name="ypeer">Y-Peer Club intend to serve as the unalterable, fundamental platform for
        young generation to sophisticate their leadership skills, to be heard and explain their basic
        core messages to the modern world. Moreover, the club could be assessed as the unique
        platform with diversified horizons, that warmly welcomes the diversity of interpretations,
        perceptions and along with that promotes the conception of pluralism. The designated club
        entirely dedicated to the construction of efficient discussion within the relevant areas,
        reshaping and properly formulating the precise visions and glances, excogitation of
        groundbreaking and innovative approaches for settling the actual problematic issues.


    </string>
</resources>